拉杰是宫保鸡丁
Let's see, Raj was the Kung Pao Chicken.
我是饺子
I'm the dumplings.
没错
Yes, you are.
太恶心了  霍华德
Creepy, howard.
恶心得可爱还是纯粹的恶心
Creepy good or creepy bad?
谁点的鲜虾加龙虾酱
Who was the shrimp with lobster sauce?
那是我的
That would be me.
朝这里看  你这个肮脏的小美味
Come to papa, you un-kosher delight.
我这话可不光是对着食物说哦
I'm not necessarily talking to the food.
坐一边去
Sit over there.
婴儿纸巾
Baby wipe?
你干嘛用
Why do you have...
-别问  -别  别问
No, don't ask! no, don't, don't!
我来告诉你为什么
I'll tell you why.
我必须消毒我的手
I had to sanitize my hands
因为大学把 厕所里擦手的纸巾
Because the university replaced the paper towels in the rest rooms
换成了吹风机
With hot air blowers.
我怎么感觉吹风机更卫生
I thought the blowers were more sanitary.
别问啊
Really, don't.  why...?
吹风机可以说是细菌 和瘟疫的发源地
Hot air blowers are incubators and spewers of bacteria and pestilence.
老实说  用吹风机的话
Frankly, it'd be more hygienic
还不如让一只得了瘟疫的长臂猿打喷嚏打到我手干
If they just had a plague-infested gibbon
来得卫生呢
Sneeze my hands dry.
伙计们  我有一个天大的
Hey, guys, I just got the most amazing
好消息
News...
天呐  拉杰  你如果不喝醉的话
Gosh, raj, do you think you'll ever be able
是不是永远都不能在我面前说话
To talk in front of me without being drunk?
好吧  那我 就自己一个人去吃了
Okay, well, I'll just, um, go eat by myself.
佩妮  你不需要这样的
Penny, you don't have to do that.
没事  考虑到他不说话 他说的话  还有他
Oh, it's okay, between him not talking, him talking and him...
我最好还是离开吧
I'm better off alone.
再见  你这个可怜的怪人
Good-bye, you poor, strange little man.
她太贴心了
She's so considerate.
你有什么大新闻
So what's your news?
还记得那个我定位的
Remember that little planetary object
比凯伯带天体更远的那颗行星吗
I spotted beyond the kuiper belt?
哦对  2008-NQ SUB-17
Oh, yeah, 2008-nq sub-17.
或者用我的叫法  宝莱坞星
Or as I call it, planet bollywood.
由于我的发现
Anyway, because of
《人物》杂志把我提名为
My discovery, people magazine is naming me
30岁以下的30大焦点人物之一了
One of their 30 under 30 to watch.
拉杰  祝贺你
Raj... congratulations.
太棒了
That's incredible.
不好意思
Excuse me,
30岁以下的什么30大人物的什么焦点
30 what under 30  what to watch what?
30岁以下的30名值得关注的梦想家
30 visionaries under 30 years of age to watch
因为他们对自己领域的一些传统臆断提出了挑战
As they challenge the preconceptions of their fields.
让我猜百万次我都不会想到是这样
If I had a million guesses, I never would have gotten that.
真是相当酷的  他们让我和一个
It's pretty cool. they've got me in
在研究印度尼西亚饥荒问题的人一起入选
With a guy who's doing something about hunger in indonesia,
还有一位精神治疗师  他在用海豚
And a psychotherapist who's using dolphins
来感化囚犯
To rehabilitate prisoners,
还有爱伦·佩基
And ellen page,
他是那部独立电影《朱诺》里的明星
Star of the charming independent film, juno.
我绝对想上她
Oh, I'd so do her.
你连海豚都想上
You'd do the dolphins.
你在用的那个我设计的望远摄像机的固定架
Do I get an honorable mention for designing
在采访中你会不会提到
The telescope camera mounting bracket you used?
不好意思
Sorry, it's not part
这和我所要叙述的温馨故事无关
Of my heartwarming and personal narrative
我是一个从新德里来的傻男孩
In which a humble boy from new delhi overcame
我克服了贫困和歧视
Poverty and prejudice
不远万里来到了美国寻找梦想
And journeyed to america to reach for the stars.
贫困吗  你老爸是个妇科医生
Poverty?  your father's a gynecologist.
他开的是宾利
He drives a bentley.
那是租的
It's a lease.
我有点搞不懂
I'm confused.
是不是由什么行业审查委员会
Was there some sort of peer review committee
来决定选那些人
To determine which scientists would be included?
行业审查  这是《人物》杂志
Peer review?  it's people magazine.
人们选择了我
People picked me.
什么人
What people?
《人物》里的那些人啊
The people from people.
那这些到底是什么人
Yeah, but exactly who are these people?
他们有什么凭据吗
What are their credentials?
为什么他们有资格评选
How are they qualified?
偶然发现了一块在太阳系里
What makes accidentally  noticing a hunk of rock
慢悠悠地飘了几十亿年的
That's been traipsing around the solar system
大石头为什么就比其他
For billions of years more noteworthy
30岁以下科学家的成就 更加杰出呢
Than any other scientific accomplishment made by someone under 30?
天呐  我想爱伦·佩基的朋友们 不会这样损她的
Boy, I'll bet ellen page's friends aren't giving her this kind of crap.
这下你感到自豪了吗
Are you proud of yourself?
总的来说  是的
In general, yes.
《生活大爆炸》
第二季  第04集
哦  漏掉的中微子原来在这儿
Oh, there's my missing neutrino.
你就像一个不稳定的电荷一样躲躲藏藏的
You were hiding from me as an unbalanced charge,
是吗  你这个亚原子魔鬼
Weren't you, you little sub-atomic dickens?
谢尔顿
Hey, sheldon.
看啊
Hey, look,
我找到了那个中微子
Look, I found  my missing neutrino.
太好了  我们可以把他从牛奶盒上拿下来了
Oh good, we can take it off the milk carton.
走吧  我们去和拉杰道歉
Come on, we're going to apologize to raj
请他去吃晚饭
And invite him out to dinner.
道什么歉
Apologize for what?
他昨天带了一个好消息来
He came over last night with some pretty good news
但我们都很不热情
And we weren't very supportive.
我感觉你像是要说什么
I sense you're trying  to tell me something.
你昨天相当欠扁
You were a colossal asshat.
没有吧
No, I beg to differ.
在我们3个人之间  我是最热情的一个
Of the three of us, I was by far  the most supportive.
是吗  来说说
Really? do tell.
如果拉杰的朋友们把门槛降低的话
How will raj ever reach true greatness
他怎么能找到科学的真谛呢
If his friends lower the bar for him?
我11岁的时候
When I was 11,
我妹妹给我爸买了一个
My sister bought our father
写着"世界上最好的爸爸"字样的咖啡杯
A "world's greatest dad" coffee mug
老实说  他一生就这么晃荡下去了
And, frankly, the man coasted until the day he died.
那么这么说吧
Okay, let's try it this way.
如果这个什么《人物》杂志 是拉杰能得到的最高成就呢
What if this people magazine thing is the best raj is ever going to achieve?
这我到没想到
I had not considered that.
走吧
Come on.
我总是忘了普通人是有极限的
I often forget other people have limitations.
真是悲哀
It's so sad.
他能感到悲哀
He can feel sadness?
不太能
Not really.
我们管这个叫自以为是
It's what you and I would call condescension.
我们进去的时候 得让他觉得我们为他高兴
Now when we go in there, let's show raj that we're happy for him.
看是我不觉得啊
But I'm not.
那就装得高兴
Well, then fake it.
你看我
Look at me.
我可以完全不去想 如果没有我的电子望远镜
I could be grinding on the fact that without my stabilizing telescope mount
他永远也不能发现 那块愚蠢的宇宙垃圾
He never would have found that stupid, little clump of cosmic schmutz.
我很牛吧
But I'm bigger than that.
好了
Fine.
那你让我怎么做
What do you want me to do?
笑
Smile.
太可怕了
Oh, crap, that's terrifying.
我们是去看库萨帕里 不是去干掉蝙蝠侠
We're here to see koothrappali, not kill batman.
笑不露齿
Try less teeth.
差不多了
Close enough. come on.
嗨  拉杰
Hey, raj.
怎么了
Hey, guys.   what's up?
我们今天晚上想请你吃饭
We just wanted to invite you out to dinner tonight.
庆祝一下你的大器早成
To celebrate your "30 under 30" thing.
对吧  谢尔顿
Right, sheldon?
你们太好了
That's very nice of you.
我很乐意去
I would like that.
-孩子们  -盖博豪斯博士
Hello, boys. dr. gablehauser.
库萨帕里博士
Dr. koothrappali.
盖博豪斯博士
Dr. gablehauser.
-霍夫斯塔德博士  -盖博豪斯博士
Dr. hofstader. dr. gablehauser.
-库珀博士  -盖博豪斯博士
Dr. cooper. dr. gablehauser.
沃罗威茨先生
Mr. wolowitz.
孩子们  我有个问题要问你们
Boys, I've got a question for you
这个房间里
Who in this room
谁发现了颗星星[恒星]
Discovered a star?
事实上  2009-NQ SUB-17只是颗行星
Actually, 2008-nq sub-17 is a planetary body.
我不是在说你  是说我呢
I'm not talking about you,  I'm talking about me.
你  我来自异国他乡的青年朋友
You, my exotic young friend,
就是我的明星
Are my star.
但他不是你发掘出来的
But you didn't discover him.
你以前都不会留意到他
You merely noticed he was here,
就跟他也没怎么留意过2008-NQ SUB-17
Much like he did with 2008-nq sub-17.
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
不好意思
Oh, sorry.
孩子  我们真该给你换个好点的办公室
Boy, we've got to get you into a better office.
能配得上你的名气
Something more suited to your status.
真的不用麻烦了
Really, you don't have to go to any trouble.
我把你安排到冯·哥图尔以前的办公室怎么样
How about if I put you in von gerlich's old office?
我更喜欢菲什宾的  更宽敞一点
I'd rather have fishbein's. it's bigger.
等等  自打菲什宾穿浴袍出现在办公室那天
Wait a minute, I called dibs on fishbein's office
我就申请他的办公室了
The day he started showing up at work in his bathrobe.
能给他换办公室  就不能
He gets a new office, I can't even get
-在男厕所放点擦手巾  -谢尔顿
-Paper towels in the men's room? -sheldon.
该死  真难为我了
Damn, this is hard.
让我问问你们
Let me ask you something.
你们觉得咱们的工作为的是什么
What do you think the business of this place is?
科学
Science
-是钱  -告诉过你吧
-Money. -told you.
这孩子的照片上了《人物》周刊
And this boy's picture in people magazine
能给我们带来多少钱
Is gonna raise us a pile of money taller than...
堆起来比你高
Well, taller than you.
我有个硕士文凭的
I have a master's degree.
谁没有啊
Who doesn't?
库萨帕里博士  你有没有
Dr. koothrappali, have you ever had lunch
在院长的餐厅吃过午饭呢
In the president's dining room?
我都不知道还有专门给院长的餐厅
I didn't even know there was a president's dining room.
和食堂的食物种类一样  就是更新鲜一点
It's the same food as the cafeteria, only fresh.
走吧  小同志
Come on, little buddy.
好滴  老同志
Okay, big buddy.
大家晚上见
See you tonight, guys.
你不用笑了
You can stop smiling now.
用过美妙的午餐之后
So anyway, after a fantastic lunch,
他们就催我去《人物》周刊拍照
I was whisked off to the people magazine photo shoot...
孩子们你们去过专业拍照的地方么
Have any of you boys ever been to a photo shoot?
没啊
Uh-uh.  no.
很神奇的哦
It's fantastic.
很明显 镜头对我很有爱  我也很上镜
Apparently, the camera loves me and i, it.
我站在星空的背景前面 拍照  我摆了个这样的姿势
They shot me in front of a starry background where I posed like this.
他们要PS一个超新星进去
They're going to digitally add a supernova.
他们觉得这样能完美诠释 我辉煌的天赋
They say it's the perfect metaphor for my incandescent talent.
没错  就像一个炽热的大火球
Right, a ball of hot, flaming gas
分崩离析
That collapses upon itself.
抱歉
Excuse me.
是我的助理特雷弗打来的
Oh, it's my assistant, trevor.
我是库萨帕里
Go for koothrappali.
还给他配个助理
they gave him an assistant
我想要根笔 还得拿着剪线钳去银行
If I want a new pen, i have to go to the bank with wire cutters.
咱们已经尽到所有该尽的社会责任了吧
Have we at this point met our social obligations?
还没
Not yet.
好吧  先安排到我的日程里
Okay, just put it on  my calendar,
同时帮我想个我出席不了的理由
But start thinking of a reason why I can't go.
哦了么  我挂了
All righty? koothrappali out.
上帝保佑那孩子
God bless that boy.
没有他我非忙死不可
I don't know what I'd do without him.
你今天下午才有的助理啊
You just got him this afternoon.
没错  但我觉得我是得有个仆人
Yes, but I'm finding that having a lackey suits me.
仆人
A lackey?
不好意思  是不是法律不允许啊
Oh, I'm sorry. is that politically incorrect?
在印度  我们称其为贱民
In india, we just call them untouchables.
现在
Now?
快了
Almost.
说到贱民  我给你们带来了好消息
Speaking of untouchables, I've got great news for you guys.
这周六《人物》杂志要举行个招待会
People magazine is having a reception this saturday
我设法让你们也被邀请了
And I managed to get you invited.
切  谢了
Oh, gee, thanks.
不客气
Oh, you're welcome.
当然我没法让你们去贵宾席
Of course, I couldn't get you into the vip section
因为那是设给贵宾的
Because, you know, that's for vips
你们只是  普通人
And you guys are just, you know... p's.
在巴布亚新几内亚有一个部落
There's a tribe in papua new guinea
当一个猎人向其他部民
Where, when a hunter flaunts his success
炫耀他的成功时
To the rest of the village,
他们宰了他  并敲打他的皮做的鼓
They kill him and drive away evil spirits
以驱逐他邪恶的灵魂
With a drum made of his skin.
当然是迷信而无道理的
Superstitious nonsense, of course,
但某人可以明白他们的用意
But one can see their point.
给你  拉杰
Here you go, raj.
你或许想慢慢享用这杯
You might want to drink this one slowly.
那就周六晚上了  这么说定了
Okay. so, saturday night, can I count on my posse?
我很乐意去  拉杰  但我去不了
Gee, I'd love to, raj,  but I can't make it.
好的  莱纳德
Oh, okay. leonard?
不行  我要  不行
No, I could... no.
谢尔顿
Sheldon?
我能去  但我不想去
I can make it. but I won't.
你们在说什么
What are you guys talking about?
周六有场为我的杂志文章举行的招待会
There's a reception for my magazine article on saturday.
而你们这些家伙不准备去
And you guys aren't going?
真不敢相信
I can't believe you.
拉杰要庆祝他的惊人成就
Raj is celebrating a tremendous accomplishment
而你们甚至都不去支持他
And you're not even going to be there to support him?
惊人成就应该是
A tremendous accomplishment would be
如果他发现一个行星体
If the planetary body he discovered
正急速撞向地球  他用意念摧毁了它
Were plummeting toward earth and he exploded it with his mind.
那太酷了
That would be cool.
我得去那个招待会
I'd go to that reception.
拜托  这很重大
Come on, this is huge.
拉杰上了《人物》杂志
Raj is gonna be in people magazine,
他甚至不用搞大斯皮尔斯姐妹中的一个的肚子
And he didn't even have to knock up one of the spears sisters.
你愿意和我一起去吗
Would you like to go with me?
我当然愿意
Of course I would.
我很荣幸
I would be honored.
真的  酷
Really? cool.
替你们脸红
Shame on you guys.
看看  我约到佩妮了
Look at that, I got a date with penny.
不敢相信那花了你一整年的时间
I can't believe it took you a whole year.
现在呢
Now?
就是现在
Now.
嘿  伙计
Hey, buddy,
我要上《人物》杂志了
I'm going to be in people magazine.
上封面的时候再打给我
Yeah, call me when you're on the cover.
[查理·西恩 《好汉两个半》男主角 ]
看看你
look at you
我像正午的阳光般闪耀  不是吗
I know. I'm resplendent like the noonday sun, am I not?
先说香槟 喝得有点早  不是吗
Uh, yeah. starting with the champagne a little early, aren't you?
豪华轿车里的  他们派了辆豪华轿车
It was in the limo. they sent a limo.
我坐的是豪华轿车  我真喜欢说"豪华轿车"
I have a limo. I just love saying "limo."
你做准备的时候喝点这个
Sip on this while you're getting ready.
我准备好了
Oh, I'm ready.
你就穿这个
That's what you're wearing?
对呀  怎么了  有什么不好吗
Um, yeah. why, what's wrong with it?
没什么  只是我本来期望的更
Nothing. I was just hoping for something a little more,
疯狂些
You know, ridonkulous.
是啊  今晚的疯狂就
Mm, yeah. well, this is all the donkulous
这个样子了
You're gonna get tonight.
好好  让我们摇摆吧
Okey-dokey,  let's roll.
好了  狂欢时刻开始
All right, it's time to raise the roof!
嘿  莱纳德
Hey, leonard.
-嘿  -哥们
Hey. dude.
你看起来很不错
You look very nice.
谢谢
Thank you.
走吧
Come on.
-晚安  莱纳德  -晚安
Good night, leonard. good night.
莱纳德  看到楼下我那辆豪华轿车了吗
Hey, leonard, do you see my limo downstairs?
看到了
Yeah.
比我爷爷小时候的房子还大
It's bigger than the house my grandfather grew up in.
好极了
Terrific.
食物也更多
It has more food, too.
好了  走吧  走吧
All right, come on. come on.
嘿
Hey.
嘿  好消息
Hey, good news.
你不用再为佩妮闷闷不乐了
You don't have to sulk about penny anymore.
有成千上百个克罗地亚女人
Look, there are hundreds of croatian women
正等着你去找她们
Just waiting for you to contact them.
为了绿卡什么都行.com
Anything-for-a-greencard.com?
我可以借你我的用户名
I'll lend you my user name.
"富有的大鸡鸡"
It's "wealthy big penis."
开玩笑吧
You're joking.
你得让她们容易明白
You gotta make it easy for 'em.
她们刚开始学英语
They're just learning english.
算了
Pass.
你就在这儿郁闷着
So you're just gonna sit around here and mope
而佩妮在和快易买的阿普博士约会
While penny is out with dr. apu from the kwik-e mart?
那不是个约会  那是种族主义
It's not a date, and that's racist.
不可能是种族主义
It can't be racist.
他是《辛普森一家》中的可爱角色
He's a beloved character on the simpsons.
我们开饭吧  我好上床睡觉
Let's just eat so I can get to bed.
运气好的话 今晚我就会死于睡眠呼吸暂停
With any luck, tonight will be the night my sleep apnea kills me.
你还记得
Did you remember to ask
－西兰花要切丁  不要切丝  -是的
For the chicken with broccoli to be diced, not shredded? yes.
即使菜单上强调是"切丝"
Even though the menu description specifies "shredded"?
-是的  -黑米  不要白米饭
Yes. brown rice, not white?
-是的  -你去韩国杂货铺
Yes. did you stop at the korean grocery
-买了上等的芥末酱  -是的
And get the good hot mustard? yes.
你从市场上买了低盐酱油吗
Did you pick up the low sodium soy sauce from the market?
-是的  -谢谢 -不用
-Yes.  -Thank you.-You are welcome
你怎么去了那么久
What took you so long?
就坐下吃吧
Just sit down and eat.
好的
Fine.
行了  是切丝的  你想要我怎么样
All right, it's shredded. what do you want me to do?
我想让你拿餐之前检查一下
I want you to check before you accept the order.
抱歉
Sorry.
你是不是担心库萨帕里
Were you distracted by the possibility that koothrappali
会和佩妮上床  所以才分神的
Might have intercourse with penny tonight?
他不会和佩妮上床的
He's not going to have intercourse with penny.
那鸡肉的事就没有借口
Then there's no excuse for this chicken.
库萨帕里的境况让我想起了
You know, this situation with koothrappali brings to mind
我小时候的一件事
A story from my childhood.
太好了  又是关于狭长地带的事
Oh, goody, more tales from the panhandle.
那是德克萨斯的西北部  我来自德克萨斯东部
That's northwest texas. I'm from east texas,
高尔夫之地  越南捕虾者的故乡
The gulf region, home to many vietnamese shrimpers.
捕虾者是你故事里的主角吗
Do the shrimpers feature in your story?
不是
No.
不管怎样
Anyway,
我八岁时
When I was eight,
一辆蒙哥马利区的送货车从我们家小猫阿吉身上辗过
A montgomery ward delivery van ran over our family cat lucky.
阿吉吗
Lucky?
对  阿吉
Yes, lucky.
他不太会用反讽  不用管
He's irony-impaired. just move on.
好的  有一只叫阿吉的死猫  接着讲
Okay, dead cat named lucky. continue.
当其他人哀悼阿吉时  我想到的是它的提早离世
While others mourned lucky, I realized his untimely demise
给我提供了一个换掉他的机会
Provided me with the opportunity to replace him
找一个更符合我个人口味的宠物
With something more suited to my pet needs
一个忠实的伴侣
A faithful companion
这样我晚上睡觉时就能抱着它
That I could snuggle with at night,
而且还能阻止心灵捕手的杀害
Yet would be capable of killing upon telepathic command.
那你不想要小狗
So not a puppy?
当然  我不要步行的
Please, nothing so pedestrian.
我想要个狮身鹰首兽
I wanted a griffin.
狮身鹰首兽吗
A griffin?
对  一半是鹰  一半是狮子
Yes, half eagle, half lion.
还是一半是神话
And mythological.
毫不相关
Irrelevant.
我在研究DNA重组技术
I was studying recombinant dna technology,
我相信我能造出来一个
And I was confidant I could create one,
但我爸妈不愿意
But my parents were unwilling
找实验必须的老鹰的卵和狮子的精子
To secure the necessary eagle eggs and lion semen.
当然了  当我妹妹想要时 她能在游泳课上得到
Of course, my sister got swimming lessons when she wanted them.
谢尔顿  不是我们不喜欢关于狮子精子的故事
Sheldon, not that we don't all enjoy a good lion semen story,
只是  你到底想说什么
But... what's your point?
我想说的是如果库萨帕里得到了
My point is if koothrappali is moving on
不应该属于他的名誉而过上了新生活
To a new life of shallow undeserved fame,
也许是时候造一个更好的同伴了
Perhaps this is an opportunity to create a better cohort.
你还想培植一个新朋友
You want to breed a new friend?
是个选择  不过谁有那闲工夫
That's one option,  but who has the time?
不过想想这个  日本人
But consider this-- the japanese,
他们正在做一些关于
They're doing some wonderful work
人工智能的研究
With artificial intelligence.
现在  你把这项研究和来自迪斯尼
Now, you combine that with some animatronics
幻想者的那些电子动物们结合
From the imagineers over at disney,
咱们就能和通晓多国语言的
Next thing you know, we're playing halo
亚伯拉罕·林肯玩《光环》了[视频游戏]
With a multilingual abraham lincoln.
谢尔顿  别会错意了  不过你真是疯了
Sheldon, don't take this the wrong way, but you're insane.
可能像你说的那样吧
That may well be,
不过事实是结识新人
But the fact is it wouldn't kill us
它也不会杀了我们
To meet some new people.
我正式声明  它可能会因结识新人而杀了我们
For the record, it could kill us to meet new people.
他们可能是杀人凶手  或者未知病原体的携带者
They could be murderers or the carriers of unusual pathogens.
而且我没疯  我妈带我做过检查了
And I'm not insane. my mother had me tested.
如果我们真有了个新朋友
If we do get a new friend,
他应该是一个我们信得过的人
He should be a guy you can trust.
他应该支持你
A guy who has your back.
而且他应该有很多钱
And he should have a lot of money
居住在海滩旁边的一所酷宅
And live in a cool place down by the beach
我们可以在那举办聚会
Where we could throw parties.
他应该像我们那样热爱科技
He should share our love of technology.
他还应该认识很多的女人
And he should know a lot of women.
那就是说  钱  女人  科技
Let's see, money, women, technology.
好的  同意 我们的新朋友会是钢铁侠
Okay, we're agreed. Our new friend is going to be iron man.
欢迎光临拉杰的泰姬陵
Welcome to the raj mahal.
很不错  晚安  拉杰
It's very nice. good night, raj.
-别走  等等  今晚尚未结束  -今晚结束了
-No, no, wait. the evening's not over. -yes, it is.
没有  放上罗·凯利的歌  再做些面部吸吮
No, it's time to put on some r. kelly and suck face.
哇  今晚结束了吗
Oh, wow, is the evening over?
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait!
这是我爸妈从印度打来的
That's my mommy and daddy calling from India.
我想让你见见他们
I want you to meet my parents.
等等  见见他们
Wait. meet them?
嗨  爸妈  很高兴见到你们
Hello, mommy, daddy. good to see you.
你们怎么样  我没喝醉
How are you? I'm not drunk.
你为什么这么说
Why would you say that?
就是想找找话题
Just making conversation.
爸妈  我想让你们见见我的新马子  佩妮
Mommy, daddy, I want you to meet my new squeeze, penny.
我不是你的马子  也没有什么骡子
I'm not your squeeze. there is no squeezing.
我看不到她  把她放到摄像头里
I can't see her. center her in the frame.
好了  可爱吧
Here you go. cute, huh?
她不是印度人
She's not indian.
不是又怎么了  儿子只是在播种种子而已
So she's not indian. the boy is just sowing some wild oats.
不对  不对
No, no, no,
没有什么播种  马子还有面部吸吮
There's no sowing, no squeezing and no sucking face.
他要是把她肚子搞大了呢
What if he gets her pregnant?
你想让这个小可爱 当你孙子孙女们的妈妈吗
Is this little hotsy-totsy who you want as the mother of your grandchildren?
你有什么权利 挑选谁和我生孩子
What right do you have to pick with whom I can have children with?
好吧  拉杰  我知道你身在美国
Look, rajesh, I understand you're in america.
你想试试"当地的佳肴"
You want to try the "local cuisine."
相信我  你可不想顿顿吃
Trust me. you don't want it for a steady diet.
现在听我说
Now you listen to me.
我不是小孩了
I am no longer a child
你们不应该这么跟我说话
And I will not be spoken to like one.
先失陪一下  我要去吐了
Now if you'll excuse me, I have to go throw up.
他怎么了
What's wrong with him?
不知道
I don't know.
可能是当地佳肴的缘故
Maybe it's the local cuisine.
好吧  很高兴见到你们
Okay, well, it's nice to meet you.
我这就把你们放到这边
I'm just gonna set you on down over here.
我要走了  合十礼
And I'm gonna leave, so namaste.
还有就是  有我做儿媳  你们应该感到幸运
And fyi, you'd be lucky to have me as a daughter-in-law.
她很传统  我喜欢
She is fusty. I like that.
拉杰  你在干什么
Raj, what are you doing?
不行  纸条不行
No, no notes.
有什么要说的  当我面说
If you have something to say to me, say it.
对不起
Sorry.
没关系的  小可怜
Oh, sweetie, it's okay.